

Profile

Idealist Web Engineer with 5+ experience in Ruby on Rails, skilled in communication and team management.

Quick learner with ability to achieve organizational goals.

Good communication and interpersonal skills.

- 6 months experience in Salesforce
- 6 months experience in Angular Js

Employment History

Senior Software Engineer, TalentInc, Pune, Maharashtra, India

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

Product: resume.io, career.io

Worked in Offer-Analyzer, Career-Coaching Modules, Resume optimizer, Job tracking, Job search.

Tailor the resume to increase the job search for user.

ChargeBee Payment Gateway.

Working in other core features as well in both products.

Handle team & guide others in problem solving.

Have target to make the organisation's evaluation of 200+ Million

Technology used: Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Redis, Sidekiq

Software Engineer, Softprodigy System Solutions, Mohali, Punjab, India

AUGUST 2021 - MARCH 2022

Product: Social, Kamersin

Front end is on vuejs.

Worked on 3 types of user in Project, database, user management, Admin management system.

Software Developer, WovV Technologies, Vadodara, Gujarat, India

JANUARY 2021 - AUGUST 2021

Product: HOSPITAL MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

Project: self, Tools: Salesforce.com

- Created hospital with lab by the user, patients information can store by the user, doctor assingment to the patients by the user.
- Developed to store patients information as per the patients by the user.

Software Developer, Ajatus Software Pvt. Ltd, Bhubaneshwar, Orissa

JANUARY 2019 - JANUARY 2021

1. Product: Authority and HR MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

Created Payslip for Employee, Leave Type for Employee using HTML and CSS,
 Custom report for Notes with comment in Bootsrap.

Details

Motihari, Bihar India 9123154868, 9774234457 rickykumarj@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin

Skills

HTML & CSS

Ruby on Rails

MySql

PostgreSQL

JavaScript

Git

Jquery

Redis

Sidekiq

AngularJS

AWS EC2,S3,code commit

Salesforce(CRM)

Languages

English

Hindi

Hobbies

Cricket.

Research and implement research outputs in real world

- Developed Import and Export Payslip and bulk upload by the H.R., Action for multiple manager for verifying leaves, claims, Api and photo upload to verify the attendace of employee, google recaptcha.
- Setup ? sendgrid to fire email for leave claim, payslip, and user action with organisation

2.Product: Pie Rooms Hotel MANAGEMENT SYSTEM (Backend)

 Setup project from scratch, Developed hotel magement database, user management, Admin management system, payment management for user as well as admin, sendgrid to fire email.

3. Product: Pass Generator MANAGEMENT SYSTEM(Backend)

 Setup project from scratch, Developed Pass magement database, user management, Admin management system.

4.Product: COURT MANAGEMENT SYSTEM(Backend)

- Created 3 types of user in project, Admin, RA, Lawyer.
- Developed Api of project, database, user management, Admin management system.

5.Product: BOOK SHOP

- Setup project from scratch(Backend) with Ruby on rails and Front-end with Ionic.
- Developed customer and Shop-magement database, user management, Admin management system.

Education

B Tech -(CSE), Gandhi Institute Of Engineering and Technology, Gunupur, Orissa

JUNE 2015 - JUNE 2019

Holy Cross Higher Secondary School, +2 -Science, Dimapur, Nagaland
MARCH 2013 - MARCH 2015

Ram Janaki Higher Secondar School, 10th, Dimapur, Nagaland